jplay.eu 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy | JPLAY

SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.  
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.  
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

SECTION 2 – CONSENT

How do you get my consent?  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at support@jplay.eu

SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

SECTION 4 – STORE

Our store is based on WooCommerce online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  
Your data is stored through WooCommerce data storage, databases and the general WooCommerce application. Your data is stored on our web provider’s secure server behind a firewall. The server and all the data are stored within the EU.

SECTION 5 – PAYMENT

If you click on the checkout button to complete your purchase then WooCommerce will forward you to PayPal website where you can log in to your PayPal account or enter your credit card number. As soon as you enter PayPal, your data, including your credit card data is encrypted and secured by PayPal.

SECTION 6 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located. Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

SECTION 7 – LINKS  
When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements. 

SECTION 8 – SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. 

SECTION 9 – AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you or simply want more information, contact us at support@jplay.eu
